Mehmet Başaran

mehmet94nto@gmail.com | https://github.com/nto4/ | https://mehmetbasaran.me

05313803779 | Ankara/Turkey

Summary

I like to learn new technologies, best practices. I have experience on python, c# and javascript and i was work on .net mvc, .net core and django, im familiar linux systems, testing and QA process also im familiar ml&dl using common librarys and api. I want to work with experienced programmers, and I think I will improve myself faster and more accurately with their guidance.

Education

- Gazi University Computer Engineering Department/2020
- \cdot I was participated Linux 1, linux 1,5, network management -2 courses in LKD summer and winter camps/2017-2018

Employment

- · Angular front-end junior developer 3/2019-5/2019 (project based freelance)
- · Asp.net core mvc and angularjs junior software developer 6/2019- 10/2019 handson P.I. Works(paid internship)
- · Junior full stack web developer Django-Emberjs 10/2019-2/2020(part-time)
- · Systems Support Specialist 7/2020-9/2020 Profelis Bilişim

Skills

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- · C# asp.net mvc& asp.net mvc core
- · Python and django rest
- · Object oriented programing & Functional programming
- · IavaScript, es6

SECONDARY LANGUAGES

- · Shell (bash, powershell)
- · Sql DDL &DML
- · Python scripting

OTHER SKILS & FAMILIAR CONCEPTS AND FRAMEWORKS

- · Gnu/Linux familiar forme; centos, redhat and debian
- · Experienced on Mysql, Sqlite and Postgresql 1 can write DDL & DML querys
- · Testing, Quality Assurance
- · Machine Learning & Deep learning using scikit learn, tensorflow, keras, pandas, numpy, Spyder

CERTIFICATES

LE-1: Linux Essentials

https://cs.lpi.org/caf/Xamman/certification/verify/LPI000460851/7y4apbwguz